CONTACT

Email: monchingcreates@gmail.com | +1 (360) 628-0868 | Seattle, WA 98108 LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ramonvidallon | Github: github.com/ramonavidallon

Portfolio: ramonavidallon.github.io/porfolio-remix

SUMMARY

Web developer who fully embodies the culture of technology. 3+ years of management in retail and healthcare; possesses excellent time management skills and the ability to grasp new concepts quickly and efficiently. Has a strong passion for UI and front end development and successfully collaborates in a diverse team environment utilizing strong interpersonal skills.

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML5
jQuery
MySQL
MERN Stack
PHP
MS Office
Javascript
Node
WordPress
EPIC

APPLICATIONS BUILT

Divvy

A bill splitting application for those who share a home or business. Responsible for the Front end/UI.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Node, Express, Sequelize

Application: https://divvy-application.herokuapp.com/

Github Repository: https://github.com/ramonavidallon/Divvy.git

<rendezvous />

An event organizing application targeted towards people in tech. Responsible for Front end/UI.

Technologies: MERN stack, Redux, Material UI **Application:** <u>https://code-meetup.herokuapp.com</u>

Github Repository: https://github.com/ramonavidallon/Code-Meetup.git

Memory Game

A memory click built with React.

Technologies: React, JS, Javascript, HTML, CSS

Application: <u>https://ramonavidallon.github.io/clicky-game/</u>

Github Repository: https://github.com/ramonavidallon/clicky-game.git

Vanilla JS Calculator

A simple calculator built with vanilla JS **Technologies:** HTML, CSS, Javascript

Application: https://ramonavidallon.github.io/vanilla-js-calculator/

Github Repository: https://github.com/ramonavidallon/vanilla-js-calculator.git

EXPERIENCE

Aloha Cup Bap

February 2018 – January 2020

Shift Supervisor Seattle, WA

- Managed daily operations with a team of 5
- Serviced customers throughout the day and educated them about menu items and poke styles
- Managed the schedule through Homebase
- Worked during busy hours and assisted in the back of house when needed
- Promoted business through the company Instagram and social media
- Assisted in hiring and onboarding for new employees

Kaiser Permanente

September 2017 – August 2019

Business Operations Float Lead Seattle, WA

- Responsible for the performance of the Primary Care front desk team
- Worked close with the Business Operations Manager to complete tasks
- Built and maintained appointing templates for medical staff
- Worked with new patients to complete registration

- Ensured patient satisfaction through customer service and patient empathy
- Worked on lengthy team projects involving private patient information

Nordstrom May 2015 – July 2017 Men's Shoes/ Casual Assistant Dept. Retail Manager Tacoma, WA | Seattle, WA

- Identified and recruited top sales talent
- Developed and coached four salespeople to become Future Nordstrom Leaders (management)
- Utilized resources that were provided to manage and produce increases with new and existing clientele
- Finished top 3 in the company and #1 in the region in overall sales for Men's Shoes Department
- Responsible for 8 Pacesetters including 1 million dollar seller
- Spotlighted for Customer Service Excellence

EDUCATION

University of Washington Seattle Full Stack Development Coding Certificate

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming and market-driven skills.